[Music]
[音乐]
更具吸引力的之一
one of the more intriguing and
路易莎写的令人愉悦的机制
三十年代想出的是这个
one of the more intriguing and
delightful mechanisms that Louisa wrote
出现在每日快报
孩子们的年度数字五是
delightful mechanisms that Louisa wrote
came up with in the thirties was this
从30年代初开始就是这个
这就是所谓的狗狗问候
came up with in the thirties was this
one that appeared in The Daily Express
打开它，狗点点头，尾巴抬起
他的头向下，这是基于
one that appeared in The Daily Express
children's annual number five this was
那只狗的身体就是盒子
这在教程14中，但随后
children's annual number five this was
from the early 30s and it's this one
围绕脖子和臀部的褶皱是
是什么推动了运动，他们是
from the early 30s and it's this one
it's called a doggy greeting and as you
真的很狡猾，所以在本教程中
这就是我要解释的
it's called a doggy greeting and as you
open it the dog nods his tail goes up
显然喜欢这种机制，因为
它在同一时间出现了几次
open it the dog nods his tail goes up
and his head goes down it's based on the
他的其他几本书，所以在这
这是巴卡诺故事三
and his head goes down it's based on the
box that body of the dog is the box
在这个我必须要小心
打破机制时保持开放
box that body of the dog is the box
which is in tutorial 14 but then the
他是给予的相同机制
移动到这跳舞的手臂，就像你
which is in tutorial 14 but then the
folds around the neck and the rump are
打开和关闭传播者
移动他的手臂是相同的机制
folds around the neck and the rump are
what give the movement and they are
也建在盒子上，所以如果你看着它
侧身就可以看到这也是一个
what give the movement and they are
really cunning so in this tutorial
盒子舞者的身体是一个盒子
在顶部有一个平行的折叠
really cunning so in this tutorial
that's what I'm going to explain he
是他的头，但手臂上的动作
是同样复杂的折痕排列
that's what I'm going to explain he
obviously liked this mechanism because
使得整个运动更大
您打开和关闭点差我会
obviously liked this mechanism because
it appeared a couple more times in a
在一分钟内解释所有这些，但是有
如果我只是一个更好的例子
it appeared a couple more times in a
couple of other of his books so in this
放些东西来打开这是
博卡没有故事5
couple of other of his books so in this
one this is Baccano stories number three
还是从1930年代开始
它有这么宏伟的
one this is Baccano stories number three
and in this one I have to be careful
指挥和身体有些笨拙
但是手臂的动作真的
and in this one I have to be careful
openness when I break the mechanism
太棒了，您再从侧面看
这是一个盒子，动作就产生了
openness when I break the mechanism
he is the same mechanism to give
通过这些折叠，手臂的方式
连接到盒子的顶部
he is the same mechanism to give
movement to this dances arms so as you
首先让我解释一下这个盒子
来自教程14，这是盒子
movement to this dances arms so as you
open and close the spread the dancer
给你这两个飞机
与基地平行，它总是必须
open and close the spread the dancer
moves his arms it's the same mechanism
中间有这个支柱
推上盖子的中央
moves his arms it's the same mechanism
also built on a box so if you look at it
通常可以为您提供坚实的基础
盒子也需要一个结局
also built on a box so if you look at it
sideways on then you see this is also a
是什么将双方锁定在一个坚实的
刚性的形状，您可以看到
sideways on then you see this is also a
box the body of the dancer is a box it's
像那里的指挥模型
在盒子的两端
box the body of the dancer is a box it's
got a parallel fold on the top that it
变成像
狗模型，实际上是狗的头
got a parallel fold on the top that it
is his head but the action on the arms
本身将双方联系在一起
并使其坚硬无止境
is his head but the action on the arms
is the same complex arrangement of folds
这个盒子，但它仍然是一个盒子形状
推上盖子的中央支柱
is the same complex arrangement of folds
that gives the whole bigger movement as
推出两侧给你一个
稳定的生活来建立这些感动
that gives the whole bigger movement as
you open and close the spread I'll
最简单的部分
要解释的是这是小教堂
you open and close the spread I'll
explain all that in a minute but there's
网为此的计划是
这块短片看起来如何
explain all that in a minute but there's
one more rather nice example if I just
这是打开框的顶部
手臂向下移动，末端被卡住
one more rather nice example if I just
put something to hold that open this is
在一起，所以这是盒子的顶部
这是山谷的褶皱，这是山
put something to hold that open this is
bokar no stories number 5
折痕都在45度
然后这是我在上面写的
bokar no stories number 5
again it's from the 1930s when we open
那就是胶水，以便您可以
看到这被粘在一起
again it's from the 1930s when we open
it it's got this rather magnificent
当盒子打开和关闭手臂时
上下移动这可能是
it it's got this rather magnificent
conductor and the bodies a bit clunky
我是这三个例子中最简单的
显示给你，那是小雕像
conductor and the bodies a bit clunky
but the movement of the arms is really
接下来最简单的是导体
这是指挥家，这是一块
but the movement of the arms is really
great you look at it from the side again
那将是他的手臂，所以这是一个
山谷折这是山折这
great you look at it from the side again
it's a box and the action is generated
也是山折这是一个
山谷折这是山折这
it's a box and the action is generated
by these folds the way the arms are
放完就算是山谷褶皱
在一起这是
by these folds the way the arms are
joined onto the top of the box
看起来像是盒子的顶部
这是他的手臂要摆动
joined onto the top of the box
first of all let me explain the box this
所以当整个传播是
像这样就关闭了
first of all let me explain the box this
is from tutorial 14 this is the box it
然后当价差打开顶部时
盒子打开，他的手臂向右移动
is from tutorial 14 this is the box it
gives you these two planes that are
再一次，也许我没有说这个
我在上面涂鸦的地方
gives you these two planes that are
parallel with the base it always has to
粘在一起看看这个你可以
看到那是粘在一起的地方
parallel with the base it always has to
have this pillar coming up the middle
你只是再看看这个你
可以看看也许我能绕过这个
have this pillar coming up the middle
which pushes up the center of the lid
您可以看到框顶部的方式是
山谷然后山顶
which pushes up the center of the lid
that gives you a solid base normally the
这是一座山，但是你有
在那与那之间的那个山谷
that gives you a solid base normally the
box will also need an end on it that is
给你那宏伟的动作
所以如果我只是用
box will also need an end on it that is
what locks the two sides into a solid
盒机制，让您有个主意
将其旋转一圈，以便您了解它的状态
what locks the two sides into a solid
rigid shape and you can see that in
从侧面关闭它的顶部
盒子关闭，手臂往后退
rigid shape and you can see that in
something like the conductor model there
页面打开，盒子顶部打开
该机制的顶部打开，
something like the conductor model there
are ends on the box that are making it
手臂放下，所以是指挥
然后是我要告诉你的最后一个
are ends on the box that are making it
into a solid shape in something like the
其实是最早的
来自每日快报儿童
into a solid shape in something like the
doggy model it's actually the dog's head
年鉴这是狗，狗有两个
机制说尾巴和头部
doggy model it's actually the dog's head
itself that ties the two sides together
他们都随着价差打开而移动
看到狗的头开始向上，
itself that ties the two sides together
and makes it rigid there is no end on
传播打开狗的头滴
一直沿着尾巴
and makes it rigid there is no end on
this box but it's still a box shape with
相反，当点差关闭时
尾巴向下，当点差打开时
this box but it's still a box shape with
a central pillar pushing up the lids
尾巴出现，所以现在我来解释
我这里有两个例子
a central pillar pushing up the lids
pushing out the sides giving you a
尾部这是背面
当它关闭时是尾巴
pushing out the sides giving you a
stable solid life to build these moving
当传播打开尾巴出现我
可以在这里展示给你看
stable solid life to build these moving
parts onto so probably the most simple
这是盒子这是尾巴
价差关闭，尾巴向下
parts onto so probably the most simple
to explain is the minuet that's this one
它散开打开尾巴出现
而制作尾巴的方式是
to explain is the minuet that's this one
the net the plan for making this this is
山谷褶皱，然后这是这是一个
山谷褶皱，这是山脉褶皱，
the net the plan for making this this is
how the piece looks so this short piece
然后这是一个山谷褶皱，所以这两个
碎片会聚在一起并粘在一起
how the piece looks so this short piece
this is the top of the box as it opens
所以在这里你可以看到它是一个山谷
折两折谷折两折
this is the top of the box as it opens
the arm moves down the end is stuck
然后它的底部是一个山谷
折叠在一起的两片
the arm moves down the end is stuck
together so this is the top of the box
那是狗的尾巴，然后
这是狗的头
together so this is the top of the box
this is a valley fold this is a mountain
你的狗比较复杂
打开和关闭它启动并
this is a valley fold this is a mountain
fold the creases are both at 45 degrees
你打开它，头下来我可以
当底座关闭时放在这里
fold the creases are both at 45 degrees
and then this where I've scribbled on it
盒子的顶部是封闭的
打开框的顶部，然后打开
and then this where I've scribbled on it
that's where it glues so that you can
狗的头掉下来，我确实做了一个
在这里，这是我弄乱了尾巴
that's where it glues so that you can
see this is glued together
所以我剪掉了，但是你可以看到
是可以看到的方框
see this is glued together
as the Box opens and closes the arm
当他们推动需求时的支柱
它关闭了，狗的头抬起了
as the Box opens and closes the arm
moves up and down this is probably the
一路打开狗的头
下降，实际上要得到这个形状
moves up and down this is probably the
most simple of these three examples I'm
只是一条直条卡
卡的直条，但得到
most simple of these three examples I'm
showing you so that's the minuet the
这个特殊的形状是用
双方都以不同的方式弯曲
showing you so that's the minuet the
next most simple is the conductor so
当您查看实际模型时
顶部的方式是
next most simple is the conductor so
here's the conductor this is the piece
狗的头是两侧的
不是由一个条制成的
here's the conductor this is the piece
that would be his arm so this is a
但是双方分歧很大，所以他们不得不
切成不同的形状给你
that would be his arm so this is a
Valley fold this is a mountain fold this
那个确切的形状，这就是我所做的
在这里给你更多，如果我
Valley fold this is a mountain fold this
is also a mountain fold this here is a
只是解释说一个很
复杂的，这是狗的后背
is also a mountain fold this here is a
Valley fold this is a mountain fold this
一小会儿，你可以看到
有两个有两个山谷褶皱
Valley fold this is a mountain fold this
is a valley fold when it's all put
然后这短片是一座山
折叠，然后这很长的时间
is a valley fold when it's all put
together this is
狗的头是山谷褶皱，
那你实际上有两座山
together this is
it looks like this is the top of the box
折叠所以你去山谷山山
所有角度都被标记为105
it looks like this is the top of the box
this is his arm that's going to swing
这就是这里的大角度
80度是这个小小的
this is his arm that's going to swing
around so when the whole spread is
那是65度
在那里，然后当你看着这个你
around so when the whole spread is
closed it's right back like that and
可以看到这里从山谷开始
折，所以这第一个是山谷折
closed it's right back like that and
then as the spread opens the top of the
然后实际上有两个山褶
这个和这个是两个山
then as the spread opens the top of the
box opens and his arm moves right round
折叠，然后你得到了狗的头
这件作品会是另一个
box opens and his arm moves right round
and again up maybe I didn't say this
谷折，这将粘合在一起
像这样粘在一起，所以这一个
and again up maybe I didn't say this
where I've scribbled that's where it's
最早的弹出机制来自
三十年代初期，我认为是
where I've scribbled that's where it's
glued together see look at this you can
真的是最有趣的游戏之一
而我想做的另一件事
glued together see look at this you can
see that's where it's glued together so
添加实际上是当您查看此内容时
你看到这些大耳朵
see that's where it's glued together so
you just have another look at this you
好吧，耳朵从这些
黄带上的小三角形
you just have another look at this you
can see maybe if I hold it round this
这些是耳朵来的地方
在这里和这里，我们刚刚看到的
can see maybe if I hold it round this
way you can see the top of the box is a
有三个不同的例子
我不了解1930年代的早期机制
way you can see the top of the box is a
valley then there's a mountain the top
认为这些天你在任何书中都看到了
但这真的很好玩，所以
valley then there's a mountain the top
of this is a mountain but you've got
虽然如果他是狗的头和狗的尾巴
移动其他两个武装，所以我已经
of this is a mountain but you've got
this mountain valley in between and that
称为本教程动臂部分
三
this mountain valley in between and that
gives you that magnificent movement
[音乐]
[掌声]
gives you that magnificent movement
so if I just explain with that using the
您
[音乐]
so if I just explain with that using the
box mechanism so you get an idea I'll